[{"question":"How many percent of the planet's water do the oceans contain?","options":[{"answer":"92 %","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"97 %","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"83 %","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"88 %","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"How many targets are included in goal 14, Conserve and sustainably use the oceans, seas and marine resources for sustainable development?","options":[{"answer":"6","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"7","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"9","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"10","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"Acidification, overfishing, ocean warming and plastic/marine pollution are large contributors to the endangerment of our oceans. What is the fifth cause the UN mentions?","options":[{"answer":"Invasive species","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Overpopulation of predatory fish","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Eutrophication","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Heavy currents","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"How large share of Global annual CO2 emissions does the ocean absorb?","options":[{"answer":"1/3","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"1/4","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"1/6","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"1/8","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Approximately, how many million tons of plastic entered the ocean in 2021?","options":[{"answer":"26","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"17","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"8","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"32","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"By which year should we prevent and significantly reduce marine pollution of all kinds according to target 14.1?","options":[{"answer":"2025","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"2045","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"2020","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"2030","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Where and when took the first UN Ocean Conference place?","options":[{"answer":"2017, New York","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"2020, Oslo","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"2015, Montreal","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"2018, Paris","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"The oceans have many functions which affect human well-being to a large extent. What is not one of them?","options":[{"answer":"They provide us with water and the oxygen we breath","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"They are an important sink for greenhouse gases","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"They provide 89 % of the global food supply","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"They are the primary regulator of the global climate","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"\u201cOcean acidification is the consequence of uptake of \u2026 ? by the ocean, resulting in a decreasing pH level and increasing acidification of the ocean\u201d","options":[{"answer":"Methane","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"CO2","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Plastics","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Mercury","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"The COVID-19 pandemic caused some reduction in coastal pollution in certain areas owing to \u2026what?","options":[{"answer":"Favorable local actions","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Reduction in tourism","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Lower uptake of CO2 emissions","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Reduced overfishing","isCorrect":false}]}]